animehere.com 2016-03-14

# Private policy in anime here.

### Private Policy & Disclaimer

The privacy of our visitors to AnimeHere.Com is important to us.
    Animehere.Com is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. We may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should always check this page to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

What we collect
    We may collect the following information: name, contact information including email address, etc. What we do with the information we gather We require this information to provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons: to facilitate a specific request on our site, for example, to post a comment on anime or to subscribe to our email feed. All emails or feed subscriptions from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings. We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law to do so.

How we use cookies
     A cookie is a small file placed on your computer’s hard drive which helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. Third parties such as our advertisers may also place cookies on your browser in the course of serving ads to you based on your visit to our site and other sites on the internet. If you want to opt out of our third-party advertiser (Google Adsense)’s use of cookies, please visit the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Links to other websites
     Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

How to contact us
    If you have any questions or concerns regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at [message@animehere.com](mailto:message@animehere.com)

Legal Disclaimer for AnimeHere.Com
     No video content is held on our servers and we, AnimeHere.Com, are in no way affiliated with the video content. The video content that is displayed originates from social video websites, such as, but not limited to Veoh, YouTube, Dailymotion and Myspace TV. In case of copyright infringement, please directly contact the responsible parties.AnimeHere.Com operates as an index and database of anime content found publicly available on the internet, in principle conducting in the same way as yahoo. However, AnimeHere.Com strongly believes in the protection of intellectual property and would be willing to assist when possible and applicable. Users who upload to these websites agree not to upload illegal content when creating their user accounts. AnimeHere.Com does not accept responsibility for content hosted on third party websites, nor do we upload videos ourselves or encourage others to do so. The videos are streamed directly from the third-party video sharing services mentioned above. All other trademarks, logos, and images are the property of their respective and rightful owners.
